

Mateus Monteiro Santos

Software Developer

Education

2017 - 2023 Computer engineering Federal University of Alagoas

2017 - 2022 Gamer development School of Visual Effects

2014 - 2017 C1 course english Anglo American Culture Center

Contact

Phone +55 82 98179 7090

Email mmonteirojs@gmail.com

Links linkedin.com/in/mateusmonteiro-s github.com/mmonteiros

Profile

Full stack developer React/React Native and Ruby on Rails. Knowledge in Photoshop, Illustrator, and AdobeXD acquired with the course at the Gracom School of Visual Effects, currently majoring in Computer Engineering at the Federal University of Alagoas (2017), joining the Center for Excellence in Social Technologies (NEES), Experience in the educational area, with an emphasis on Intelligent Tutors Virtual Learning Environments.

Experience

2021 - Present Front-end Developer
Fetchly Labs Development of gppli

Development of applications with React, React native, Redux and Ruby on Rails.

2019 - 2020 Technological Development and Innovation

Full-stack Developer

Development of a mobile application using React Native, Redux, and Firebase to increase adherence to treatment.

2017 - 2021 Institute United World **Administration Secretary**

Collaborate with the improvement of the quality of life integral and economic autonomy of families peasant women preserving the base of support of life: natural resources.

Skills

React/Jest Ruby On Rails Ruby On Rails Angular/Karma Java Python